Barbara B. Kennelly Papers
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Subject Files, 1978-1998
  - Subseries E: 100th Congress, 1987-1988
    - Historic Rehabilitation, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 8)
    - Hubbell, Inc. - (Woods Problem), 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 9)
    - Insurance - State Risk Pools Ad, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 10)
    - International Associsation of Fire Chiefs - "Effective Ways of Communicating with Congress" - Hartford, CT, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 11)
    - Katherine Gibbs School - Commencement - Norwalk, CT, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 12)
    - Law Day - Hartford, CT, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 13)
    - Medicare - Catastorphic Health Insurance, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 14)
    - Minority Hiring - Hartford Courant Letter to Editor {also clips}, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 15)
    - Mt. Holyoke Club - "Women in Politics: Still Pioneers?" New York, NY, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 16)
    - National Journal - Congress's Rising Stars - Jan. 24 1987/No. 4 (Box 18:, Folder 17)
    - New England Council - Conference on Competativeness, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 18)
    - New England Monthly, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 19)
    - New England Sunday Taping, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 20)
    - Oil Import Fee, 1986-1987 (Box 18:, Folder 21)
    - Oil Import Fee - Budget Resolution, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 22)
    - Oil Import Fee - Northeast Midwest Congressional Coalition, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 23)
    - Pension Bill - Economic Equity Act, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 24)
    - Political Tax Credit, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 25)
    - Questionairre - Successful Woman Magazine, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 26)
    - Questionnaire - Women for Racial and Economic Equality, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 27)
    - Quinnipiac College - Laurel Girl's State, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 28)
    - Radcliffe College - Alumnae Award, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 29)
    - Radcliffe College - Reunion - "Women in Action" [Speech, letters, Info], 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 30)
    - Retiement Equity Act - HR 2613, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 31)
    - Route 6 Project, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 32)
    - Rural Letter Carriers, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 33)
    - Service Sector Data Collection Act of 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 34)
    - Small Business Trade, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 35)
    - Smith College - Women in Politics Lecture Series - North Hampton, MA, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 36)
    - Soviet Jewry - Ida Nudel [letter, record], 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 37)
    - Sports Ticket Pickle, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 38)
    - Tax - CIA / AIG Second Problem, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 39)
    - Tax - Connecticut Municipal Power Problem, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 40)
    - Tax - Dick & Sophie Moore, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 41)
    - Tax - Hartford Fire Insurance Company, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 42)
    - Tax - Westfield Problem, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 43)
    - Trade - Offsets, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 44)
    - Trade - Textile and Apparel Trade Act, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 45)
    - Trade Trip, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 46)
    - Union Station, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 47)
    - United Technologies Corporation - "Woods" Transition Rules, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 48)
    - Van Pooling, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 49)
    - Wadsworth Antheneum (Simpson Collection), 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 50)
    - Welfare Reform, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 51)
    - Yale Univeristy, 1987 (Box 18:, Folder 52)
    - American Council of Life Insurance, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 53)
    - B+B Associates - Day Care Award, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 54)
    - BBK Accomplishments 100th Congress, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 55)
    - Bethel African Methodist Church Humanitarian Award - Acceptance Speech, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 56)
    - Biographies, 1986-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 57)
    - Blind Pools, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 58)
    - Capitol Commentaries, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 59)
    - Coalition for Women Appointments - Remarks on Dukakis, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 60)
    - Connecticut Economic Perspective, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 61)
    - Democratic Convention - Rules Committee, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 62)
    - Democratic Leadership Council (DLC) - Panel on National Service, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 63)
    - Faculty Housing Conference, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 64)
    - Financial Institutions Retirement Fund, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 65)
    - Hartford Courthouse, 1987-1988 (Box 18:, Folder 66)
    - Hartford Public High School - 350th Anniversary, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 67)
    - Hate Crimes, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 68)
    - Hate Crimes - Synagogue Arson in West Haven, 1988 (Box 18:, Folder 69)
    - Hurricane Gilbert, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 1)
    - Infant Mortality Press Conference, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 2)
    - Insurance - BBK Insurance Ammendment, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 3)
    - Insurance - Kennelly-Guarini Amendment, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 4)
    - Ireland - Northern Ireland Fair Employment Act, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 5)
    - Jim Wright Inquiry, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 6)
    - Kiddie Tax - HR5063, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 7)
    - Life Insurance Fact Book, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 8)
    - Medicare - Foot Care Bill, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 9)
    - Memorial Day - Newington, CT, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 10)
    - Moore McCormack Resources, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 11)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews - Human Relations Award - Personal Remarks, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 12)
    - National Journal Update - BBK in 99th, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 13)
    - Partnership for Long Term Care Act of 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 14)
    - Press Questions and Accompanying BBK Quotes/Statements, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 15)
    - Questionnaires, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 16)
    - Tax - Authors / Capitalization, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 17)
    - Tax - CIGNA - Chain Deficit Rule, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 18)
    - Tax - Mary Wade Home-IRS Problem, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 19)
    - Tax Treatment - Child Support and Alimony (W&M), 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 20)
    - Title XX Funding - [PR, Letters], 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 21)
    - Trade - Connecticut Conference on International Trade, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 22)
    - Transportation - Charter Oak Bridge, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 23)
    - Union Pond / Hockanum River Water Project, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 24-25)
    - Van Pools, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 26-27)
    - Ways and Means - Life Insurance Hearing, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 28-29)
    - Ways and Means - Single Premium, 1988 (Box 19:, Folder 30-31)
    - Ways and Means - Single Premium and Investment Oriented Insurance, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 1)
    - Ways and Means - Single Premium Testimony Before Ways and Means Subcommittee, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 2)
    - Women's Veterans Memorial - Testimony, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 3)
    - Young Israel of Stamford - Award Acceptance Speech, 1988 (Box 20:, Folder 4)
  - Subseries F: 101st Congress, 1989-1990
    - Bradley Airport - KLM, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 5)
    - Budget - Reconciliation Conference Committee, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 6)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE), 1987-1989 (Box 20:, Folder 7-9)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Interstate Computers, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 10)
    - Corporation for Independent Living, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 11)
    - Democratic Caucus Chair, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 12-13)
    - Doc Hurley Scholarship IRS, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 14)
    - Eastern Europe Trip, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 15)
    - Ethics - Jim Wright, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 16)
    - El Salvador, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 17)
    - ESOP Transition Rules, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 18)
    - First Night Hartford, Inc. (IRS), 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 19)
    - Hedge Bond Transition Problem, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 20)
    - Historic Preservation (Basic Material), 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 21-22)
    - Historic Rehabilitation - Tax Reform - BBK Amendment, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 23)
    - Insurance - Final Treasury and GAO Life Insurance Reports, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 24)
    - Insurance - Possible Insurance Related Amendments and Positions, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 25)
    - Intelligence Authorization Bill, 1989 (Box 20:, Folder 26)
    - Life Insurance Hearing, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 1-2)
    - Long-term Care Bill, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 3)
    - Loomis Chaffee School, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 4)
    - Mammography Material, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 5-7)
    - Medicare - Catastophic Hearings, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 8)
    - Medicare - Catastrophic - Florida, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 9-10)
    - Medicare - Catastrophic - G, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 11-13)
    - National Journal - BBK Named in Article on "Designated Hitters", 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 14)
    - National Service: Impact Briefing Workshop on National Service, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 15)
    - National Service Plan, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 16-17)
    - Peace Corps Bill, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 18)
    - Pension Bill, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 19)
    - Pension Reform Act, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 20)
    - Puerto Rico - Hurricane Hugo, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 21)
    - Resolution to Commemorate Pay Telephone {Press Release}, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 22)
    - Romania, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 23)
    - Single Premium Life II, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 24)
    - The Urban Institute, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 25)
    - Transition Rule, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 26)
    - Transportation Appropriations Bill, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 27)
    - University of Connecticut Controversy, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 28)
    - University of Hartford, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 29)
    - Van Pool Bill, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 30)
    - War on Drugs - Connecticut, 1989 (Box 21:, Folder 31)
    - Ways and Means - 1989 Reconciliation - Additional Items (Box 22:, Folder 1)
    - Ways and Means - Catastrophic, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 2-3)
    - Ways and Means - Health Markup, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 4-5)
    - Ways and Means - Markup, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 6-8)
    - Ways and Means - Rehabilitation Testimony, 1989 (Box 22:, Folder 9)
    - 9th Square Project, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Funding, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 11)
    - Air Force - Defense Contracts, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 12)
    - BBK History, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Finance Reform, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 14)
    - Child Care Conference, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 15)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Commision - Background on Members, 1989-1990 (Box 22:, Folder 16)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Golden Heart Award, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 17)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - International, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 18)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - National Child Support Enforcement Association Annual Conference - Keynote Speech, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 19)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Visitation, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 20)
    - Cigars, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 21)
    - Civil Rights Act of 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 22)
    - Clean Air Bill - Pratt and Whitney Amendment, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut - Governor, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 24)
    - Corporate Owned Life Insurance (COLI), 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 25)
    - El Salvador - Trip, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 26)
    - Energy - Gas, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 27)
    - Energy Conservation Bill, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 28)
    - Enterprise Zone Bill, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 29)
    - First 1990 Campaign (Box 22:, Folder 30)
    - Food Stamps at Farmer's Market, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 31)
    - Francisco Borges - Teasurer of Connecticut, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 32)
    - Government Sponsored Entities, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 33)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 34)
    - Hall High School - Environment Speech, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 35)
    - Hartford - Housing and Urban Development Grants, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 36)
    - Hartford - Hunger, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 37)
    - Hate Crimes Statistics Act, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 38)
    - Historic Preservation - Weir Farm, 1990 (Box 22:, Folder 39)
    - Home Heating Oil - Investigation, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 1)
    - Home Heating Oil - Legislation, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 2)
    - Home Heating Oil - Tax, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 3)
    - Homebuilders - Contributions, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 4)
    - House Democratic Steering and Policy Committee, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 5)
    - Junior League of Hartford, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 6)
    - Machine Tools, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 7)
    - Mammography, 1989-1990 (Box 23:, Folder 8)
    - Markup Issues Background, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 9)
    - Medicare - Catastrophic, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 10)
    - Medicare - Long Term Care, 1988-1990 (Box 23:, Folder 11-17)
    - Medicare - Long Term Care and Accelerated Death Benefits, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 18)
    - Medicare - Long Term Care Waiver, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 19)
    - Medicare - Solvency, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 20)
    - Mid East - Diplomatic Solution to Persian Gulf, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 21)
    - Mid East - Persian Gulf Trip, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 22)
    - Moffett, Toby, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 23)
    - Most Favored Nation Status - Eastern Europe, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 24)
    - National Service Legislation, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 25)
    - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 26)
    - Newsletter Follow Up, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 27)
    - Newsletter Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 28-29)
    - Nicaragua - Nun Slain, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 30)
    - NOAA-Regional Climate Centers, 1989-1990 (Box 23:, Folder 31)
    - Older Womens Breast Cancer Prevention Act, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 32)
    - Poland - Border, 1990 (Box 23:, Folder 33)
    - Questionnaire - Kennelly Health Care, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 1)
    - Questionnaire - AFL/CIO, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 2)
    - Questionnaires, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 3)
    - Rostenkowski - City Funding, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 4)
    - Social Security - Disability Benefits for Widows, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 5)
    - Social Security - Women and Children, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 6)
    - South Ameica, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 7)
    - Strategic Pertroleum Reserve, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 8)
    - Tax - Bill to Close S&L Loopholes - HR 5673, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 9)
    - Tax - State and Local Deductions, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 10)
    - Textile, Apparel, and Footwear Trade Act, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 11)
    - Transportation - Appropriations Bill, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 12)
    - Transportation - Bradley International Airport, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 13)
    - University of New Haven - Commencement, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 14)
    - Ways and Means - Family Support Act, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 15)
    - Ways and Means - Letters, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 16)
    - Ways and Means - Life Care Facility Transition Rules, 1989-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 17)
    - Ways and Means - Life Insurance - Small Company Relief - Belas, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 18)
    - Ways and Means - Life Insurance - Taxation - Mike Prucker, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 19)
    - Ways and Means - Life Insurance - Taxation, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 20-24)
    - Ways and Means - Salvage and Subrogation, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 25-26)
    - Ways and Means - Section 89 Markup, 1989-1990 (Box 24:, Folder 27-28)
    - Ways and Means - Taxation of Life Insurance Companies, 1990 (Box 24:, Folder 29-30)
  - Subseries G: 102nd Congress, 1991-1992
    - AFDC Micro Enterprise Bill, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 31)
    - AFDC Microenterprises Bill, 1990-1991 (Box 24:, Folder 32)
    - AIDS - Funding, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 33)
    - Baltic States, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 34)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - CSENET, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 35)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Questions for HHS Inspector General, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 36)
    - Community Revitalization Tax Act, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 37)
    - Connecticut Federal Employee's Pay Raise Bill - HR 1298, 1991 (Box 24:, Folder 38)
    - Corporate Owned Life Insurance (COLI), 1990-1991 (Box 25:, Folder 1-2)
    - Defense - Connecticut National Guard Concerns about Defense Conference Report, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 3)
    - Defense - House Saves National Guard Jobs, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 4)
    - Defense - Letter on B2 Bomber and Strategic Defense Initiative, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 5)
    - Delegation Action, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 6)
    - Department of Defense - Family Policy, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 7)
    - EITC Problems, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 8-9)
    - Energy Conservation Tax, 1990-1991 (Box 25:, Folder 10-12)
    - Environment - Interior Appropriations, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 13)
    - Equal Remedies Act of 1991 - HR 3975 (Box 25:, Folder 14)
    - Family Medical Leave Floor, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 15)
    - FBI - Critical Skills Scholarship Program, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 16)
    - Government Sponsored Entities (GSE's) - Treasury Report, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 17)
    - Gulf War, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 18)
    - Hartford - Grants, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 19)
    - Hartford - Riverfront Recapture, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 20)
    - Health, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 21)
    - Health Access and Affordibility Today Act, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 22)
    - Health Care - CT Small Group Reform, 1990-1991 (Box 25:, Folder 23-24)
    - Health Care - Prepayment of Death Benefits Bill, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 25)
    - Health Care Newsletter, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 26)
    - Heublein, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 27)
    - Hunger - Select Committee on Hunger, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 28)
    - Infant Mortality Funding, 1991 (Box 25:, Folder 29)
    - Labor: Striker Replacement, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 1)
    - Leadership Items, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 2)
    - Legislation - 102nd Congress, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 3)
    - Machine Tools, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 4)
    - Mammography Bill, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 5)
    - Medicare - Long Term Care Bill, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 6)
    - Mortgage Revenue Bond (MRB) Legislation - San Fransico Charge, 1990-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 7)
    - Most Favored Nation Status - Romania, Bulgaria, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 8)
    - Nuclear Waste - Connecticut Sites, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 9)
    - Peace Corps - Armenia, Ukraine, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 10)
    - Pension - BBK Calls For Investigation Into Standard-Knapp and Raymark Corps., 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 11)
    - Planned Parenthood - Public Service Award, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 12)
    - Pratt and Whitney - Advanced Tactical Fighter (ATF) Contract, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 13)
    - Questionnaires, 1988-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 14)
    - SSI/SSA Disability for Widows, 1990-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 15)
    - Tax - Close Savings and Loan Tax Loopholes - HR 5673, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 16)
    - Tax - Hartford Heating/Cooling District Board Transition Rule, 1986-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 17)
    - Tax - Variable Retired Lives Reserves, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 18)
    - Timex, 1985-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 19)
    - Transportation - Kennelly Sites, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 20)
    - Transportation Appropriations Bill - Bradley, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 21)
    - Urban Caucus, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 22)
    - US Food Agency - Low-income Nutrition, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 23)
    - UTC Layoffs, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 24)
    - Ways and Means - Health Care - Welfare, 1990-1991 (Box 26:, Folder 25-28)
    - Ways and Means - Tax - HR 3909, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 29)
    - Ways and Means Subcommittee on Health Comes to Hartford, 1991 (Box 26:, Folder 30)
    - AIDS, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 31)
    - Budget - Balenced Budget, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 32)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Child Support Hearings, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 33-35)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - GAO Report, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 36)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Hearing on Downey/Hyde Proposal, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 37)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Legislation, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 38)
    - Child Support Enforcement (CSE) - Press Conference, 1992 (Box 26:, Folder 39)
    - Civil Rights - Rodney King, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 1)
    - Community Development Block Grant, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut - Fedral Funding, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut Police and Fire, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Transportation Priorities, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 5)
    - Cosponsorships 102nd, 1991-1992 (Box 27:, Folder 6)
    - Defense - 76th Reserve Division, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 7)
    - Defense - Cuts, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 8)
    - Defense - Economic Conversion Amendment, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 9)
    - Defense - National Guard Cuts in Connecticut, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 10)
    - Defense Conversion Comission Hearing, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 11)
    - Defense Economic Reinvestment Act - HR 4927, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 12)
    - Disaster Relief Appropirations - Summer Jobs in Connecticut, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 13)
    - Education Remarks/Updates, 1988-1992 (Box 27:, Folder 14)
    - Emergency Unemployment Compensation Program, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 15)
    - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 16)
    - Health Care, 1990-1992 (Box 27:, Folder 17)
    - Health Care - Colin's Health Files, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 18-21)
    - Health Care - Problems to be Solved in Stark Health Bill, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 22)
    - Health Care Questionnaire Results, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 23)
    - Historic Preservation - Weir Farm, 1992 (Box 27:, Folder 24)
    - Historic Preservation, 1990-1992 (Box 27:, Folder 25-28)
    - Issues, 1990-1992 (Box 28:, Folder 1)
    - League of Women Voters of Connecticut, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 2)
    - Medford Declaration, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Day, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 4)
    - MGC / RLR Amendment, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 5)
    - Modified Guarenteed Contracts, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 6)
    - Mortgage Revenue Bonds, 1990-1992 (Box 28:, Folder 7-8)
    - Mortgage Revenue Bonds 2, 1990-1992 (Box 28:, Folder 9-10)
    - NARFE, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 11)
    - National Displaced Homemakers Network, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 12)
    - Newington Children's Hospital, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters List, 1982-1992 (Box 28:, Folder 14)
    - NIH Reauthorization Bill, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 15)
    - Old State House, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 16)
    - Questionnaire - AFL/CIO, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaires - Campaign, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 18)
    - Questionnaires, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 19-20)
    - South Africa - BBK Letter to President Bush, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 21)
    - Tax - First Time Home Buyers Credit, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 22)
    - Tax - Unemployment, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 23)
    - Trinity College - Presidential Leadership Award, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 24)
    - University of Connecticut, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 25-26)
    - Ways and Means - Accomplishments for 102nd Congress, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 27)
    - Ways and Means - Accomplishments for Women on Ways and Means, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 28)
    - Ways and Means - Women and Ways and Means - History, 1992 (Box 28:, Folder 29)
  - Subseries H: 103rd Congress, 1993-1994
    - Airline Industry, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Abortion Post Cards, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 2)
    - BBK Files / Important Memos, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 3)
    - Bushnell Park, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 4)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Retirement and Disability System (CIARDS), 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 5)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 6)
    - Child Support Enforcement, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 7)
    - Children's Hospital, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 8)
    - Colt - Assault Weapons Ban, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 9)
    - Colt - M4 Carbine, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut (CT) Public Television, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 11)
    - Crime, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 12)
    - Dear Colleague's (DC's) and Bills - 103rd Congress, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 13)
    - Defense - Economic Conversion Bill, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 14-15)
    - Defense - M1 A2 Tank Upgrade, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 16)
    - Defense - UConn Summit, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 17)
    - Economic Adjustment Bill, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 18)
    - Handicapped Parking Bill, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 19)
    - Health / CT Long-term Care, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 20)
    - Home Heating Oil - Tax Exemption, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 21)
    - International Fuel Cells, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 22)
    - Locality Pay OPM/M&G, 1993 (Box 29:, Folder 23-24)